m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯：Bazinga   胡好時   foxer   魚骨頭
校對：原子蛋    總監   原子蛋
后期：加森     時間軸：sagelibra  今
南方公園  第十七季第七集
黑色星期五
I'm going down to south park
gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere
humble folks without temptation
Going down to south park
gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night
people shouting howdy neighbor
Heading on out to south park
gonna see if I can't unwind
I like girls with big vaginas
I like girls with big fat titties
Come on down to south park
and meet some friends of mine.
黑色星期五
11月29日
南方公園商場
黑色星期五促銷
凜冬將至
到了節日季
The holiday season is here.
黑色星期五也不遠了
And Black Friday is upon us.
要知道  黑色星期五那天
As you know, Black Friday is the day
顧客會因假日促銷暴走
shoppers go berserk for holiday deals.
去年26人遇難
Last year 26 people died
461人受重傷
and 461 were seriously injured.
今年冬天  商場向前20位來店顧客
This winter, the mall is offering 80% off
給出2折優惠
to the first 20 people in the store.
你們這些新來的應聘這份工作
For you new recruits perhaps you took this job
或許只想見見世面
to see just what the balance was like
或許你覺得
or perhaps you thought
黑色星期五上班沒啥大不了的
working Black Friday wouldn't be a big deal.
我不過是想節假日賺點外快
I'm just trying to earn extra holiday cash.
或許你太蠢了
Or maybe you're too stupid to
都沒意識到自己跳進了火坑
realize what you've gotten yourself into.
夠了
That's enough.
我們今年只有齊心協力才能
Our only chance to survive in this year's sale
在這場促銷浩劫中存活下來
is by sticking together.
你們應征入伍值得表揚  不過我警告你們
Those of you who signed up are to be commended but I warn you,
千萬不要低估門外
do not underestimate the battle that's
即將到來的惡戰
about to take place outside those doors.
凜冬將至
Winter is coming.
晚上好  先生
Good evening, sir.
我在召集所有的戰士
I'm calling together all the fighters of Zaron.
我有事要和麥考米克夫人談
I need to speak with Lady McCormick.
她現在不在
She's not here right now.
請轉告她來參加大禮堂的會議
Please tell her there's to be a meeting in the great hall.
我已經想到搶XBOX的方法了
I have found a way to get Xbox ones
尊敬的麥考米克夫人應該會感興趣的
and the Fair Lady McCormick will want to hear about it.
感謝各位的到來
Thank you all for coming.
托肯王子
Prince Token,
黑湖的蒂米爵士
Sir Timmy of Blacklake,
麥考米克夫人
Lady McCormick.
勇士們  我們曾無數次并肩作戰
Warriors, we have fought many great battles together
在克萊德家  在斯考特·梅爾·金森家
at Clyde's house, and Scott Mel Kinson's House.
不過我們馬上就要展開
But soon we'll be fighting
一場有生以來最慘烈的戰斗
the greatest battle of our young hard lives.
凜冬將至
Winter is coming.
新一代游戲設備又將紛紛上架
And the next gen gaming devices are hitting the shelves.
可沒人買得起
Which nobody can afford.
要是我跟你們說  如果我們齊心合力
What if I would tell you that we all work together
就有辦法搞到新一代的游戲機
there's a way we can get the new gaming system?
巫師  如果你有辦法就說出來
If you know of a way, Wizard, then speak.
我在工作中學會了一種黑魔法
I've learned of a dark magic at work.
感恩節過后的第一天
The day after Thanksgiving,
前30位進商場的將獲得全場2折優惠
the first 30 people inside the mall get 80% off whatever they want.
他們稱之為黑色星期五
They're calling it Black Friday.
好怕怕
Woo, Spooky.
黑色星期五
Black Friday?
拜托  沒那回事兒
Come on, that can't be real.
真有  克雷格
It is real, Craig,
我在新聞上看到的  混蛋
I saw it on the news, butthole.
真有其事
It is real.
每年都有
They do it every year,
可全城上下都想在黑色星期五
but Everyone in town tries to be
第一個擠進商場
the first inside the mall on Black Friday.
我們勝算有多大
What chance do we have?
純靠我們自己  沒可能
On our own, none.
但只要計劃周密  深謀遠慮  合力奮戰
But if we plan, strategize and fight together,
我們就能成為黑色星期五第一批進去的人
we could be the first people inside on Black Friday.
然后憑著2折優惠得到我們用來救命的
And use the 80% to get the gaming system we need
游戲機
to survive.
感恩節快到了  我們都知道這意味著什么
Well, it's almost Thanksgiving and we all know what that means.
沒錯  黑色星期五即將到來
That's right, Black Friday is just around the corner.
艾瑪
Ouch.
大家都摩拳擦掌  躍躍欲試
And people are already gearing up.
我們通常凌晨3點就來排隊了
We usually start lining up around 3 a.m..
我們把自己渾身浸滿豬血
We douse ourselves in pig blood
因為這樣能在開門的時候助我們滑過人群
because it does help us slip threw the crowd when the doors open.
我們每年都來  算是家庭傳統了
We do it every year, part of the family tradition.
去年我們不幸失去了最小的女兒
Last year we lost our youngest daughter.
她的腦袋被踩了個稀巴爛
Her head was stepped on and crushed.
不過為了紀念她  我們今年打算找個
But in her memory we're going to find a young girl
小女孩  踩她的頭
and step on her head this year.
要是有人以為 他們能在商場里打敗我
If anyone thinks they're gonna beat me inside that mall
妨礙我給孩子們買圣誕禮物
and keep me from getting my kids' christmas presents,
你丫想都別想
they can kiss my fat vagina,
因為我會讓他們生不如死
coz I'm bringing the motherfucking pain.
南方公園商場的湯姆說
Tom, the south park mall says,
他們已經加強保安戒備
they've beefed up security
力求減少今年死亡人數
in an effort to reduce the number of fatalities this year
可以肯定的是人們十分重視黑色星期五
One thing's for sure, people take Black Friday very seriously.
對  對  非常好  很好
Yes, yes. Very nice. Good.
卡特曼巫師  網上有消息  大人
Wizard Cartman, I have news from the internet, my lord.
《權力的游戲》里面的人不興敬禮  巴特斯
They don't salute in Game of Thrones, Butters.
抱歉  我還沒看過
Sorry, I haven't watched it yet.
這樣啊  那你要趕緊看了  哎呀太好了
OK. You need to start immediately please. Ah, very good!
灰鷹家族同意加入我們的戰斗了
The House of Grayhawk has agreed to join our fight.
灰鷹家族
The House of Grayhawk?
瑪麗安·布萊茨多斯基
Marian Bryostowski.
可是我的朋友 我們還得繼續尋找其他
But my friends, we must still find others
愿意同我們并肩戰斗的人
who will fight by our side.
還有沒有別的沒分派的人  能來幫幫我們
Are there no other factions we can call to our aid?
我知道
I know,
要不我們問問那些玩星際迷航的孩子吧
how about we ask those kids who play Star Trek?
才不要  去他媽的
No, screw those guys.
全是呆子  我才不要跟他們玩
They're dorks and I'm not playing with them.
我正想來點呢
Hey, that's what I'm talking about.
還有嗎
You got any extra of that?
謝謝
Oh, thanks.
這里有點無聊了
Gets a little boring around here, you know.
趁現在好好享受無聊吧
Enjoy the boredom while you can.
你去年冬天也在這工作嗎
So you worked here last winter?
黑色星期五也值班的嗎
You worked on Black Friday.
是啊
I did.
有他們描述的那么糟糕嗎
Is it really as bad as they say it is?
那些顧客
The shoppers
周四晚上便陸陸續續出現了
started showing up at midnight on Thursday.
他們沒有排隊
They didn't line up,
而是逐漸涌向正門
they just crammed themselves near the main entrance.
我能看見他們的臉貼在玻璃門上
I can see their faces smushed up against the glass
舔著舌頭  等著進來
licking their lips waiting to get in.
天哪  他們發出的那些聲音
God, the sounds they made.
5點商場門開了
It was 5 a.m. when they opened the doors.
到處都是尖叫聲  到處都是血
There was screaming, blood,
人們互相撕扯著對方的臉
people tearing each other's faces off
節日的背景音樂放得正酣
while holiday music played in the background
我看見一個女人抓起她女兒的腳踝
I saw a woman pick up her daughter by the ankle
就往一老頭頭上甩
and swing her into some old guy's head.
我還沒來得及反應  便被他們包圍了
Before I knew it they were all around me,
人們爭吵著  搶奪著
fighting, clawing.
后來一只手伸進來  把我一把揪了出來
Then a hand reached in and pulled me out.
頭兒那天救了我們所有人
Old cap. He saved us all that day.
那天打烊后
When it was over,
商場前已經血流成河
in front of the mall was covered in red,
到處都是尸體  還有購物袋
bodies, shopping bags.
黑色星期五
前30名顧客的所有商品2折
現在  冬天又要來了
And now winter comes again.
卡特曼巫師  我開始看《權力的游戲》了
Wizard Cartman, I've started watching Game of Thrones.
很好  巴特斯圣騎士  你覺得好看嗎
Ah, yes Paladin Butters, are you enjoying it?
我覺得挺不錯的
Well, it's pretty good I guess.
但你有沒注意到
But have you ever notice
每次里面露出某人的雞雞
that almost every time they show a guy's wiener,
那個角色就會搞基
that guy's character's a Gay.
你想要說什么
What do you mean?
里面出現有很多爆乳娘  寶器妹什么的
Just they have a lot of girls' boobs and vagina and stuff
但男人露雞雞的時候
but most times they show a man's wiener
大部分情況下都是在另一個男人演激情戲
is because that guy is in love scene with another guy.
你覺得這是因為
You think it's because
同性戀的雞雞對女性觀眾威脅比較小嗎
gay wienner is less threatening to women viewers?
我覺得你根本沒看到
I believe you might be missing
這部劇的重點  巴特斯圣騎士
the greater point of the show, Paladin Butters.
我知道的  凜冬將至啊
Yeah, I know. Winter's coming,
龍和喪尸們都跑出來了
and there're dragons and zombies on the way.
對此我倒是挺興奮的
I'm pretty excited for that,
這樣總算能少看點搞基的雞雞了
just can do with a little less gay wieners though.
幼兒園的那幫人給我們消息了
We have word from the kindergartners.
他們同意加入我們了
They've agreed to join us.
那些Xbox One是我們的了
Those Xbox Ones are as good as ours.
等等  Xbox One是什么意思
Wait, what are you talking about Xbox Ones?
這就是咱們的目標啊  克雷格
That's what this is all about, Craig.
咱們不就在努力爭取
We're all trying to
黑色星期五那天買Xbox One嘛
get Xbox Ones on Black Friday.
我以為我們要買的是PS4
I thought we were getting Playstation 4s.
什么
What?
我也這么以為的
Me too.
不對  哥們兒
No, guys.
當我說我們要去弄下一代的游戲系統
When I said we are gonna get the next gen gaming systems
我顯然說的是Xbox
I was obviously talking about Xboxes.
我想要PS4  而不是什么垃圾Xbox
I want a ps4, not a crappy Xbox.
聽著伙計們  我們必須得達成共識
Look guys, we all have to agree on one system.
是這樣的
That's right.
要是我們有人玩PS4
If some of us are on PS4s,
其他的玩Xbox
but rest of us on Xboxes,
那我們就沒法一起聯機了  明白嗎
then we all can't play together online. See?
所以必須要用一種機器
This is all about commiting to one machine.
好吧  那就都買PS4
Right, let's all get PS4s.
不  Xbox更棒
No, the Xboxes are gonna be better.
它們才沒有更好  它們只是更貴罷了
They're not better. They're just more expensive.
我們要買Xbox One
We're getting Xbox Ones, guys.
而且這是最終決定
And that is final.
Xbox玩家就是這樣的
That's exectly how Xbox people are.
好吧
Fine.
要是你們不愿意黑色星期五
If you guys don't want to join us
跟我們一起去弄Xbox
on Black Friday to get Xboxes,
那就算了
then that's fine.
我們黑色星期五還是會去
We're still gonna fight on Black Friday
只不過不是和你們
just not with you.
看來非得如此了是吧
Oh, it's going to be like that is it?
想要PS4的人  加入我們這邊
Everyone who wants to get PS4s, join with us.
我們不能就這樣分裂
No, we can't divide like this.
斯坦  你是我們這邊的  對嗎
Stan, you're on our side, right?
我更喜歡PS4的手柄
I like the PS4's controller better.
斯坦  PS4不能和Xbox One一樣
Stan, the PS4 doesn't have the seamless transition
在游戲動畫和電視節目間無縫切換
between games' movies and TV offered by Xbox One.
但PS4的手柄上有觸摸板啊
The PS4 controller has a touchpad interface.
你從來都聽不進去
You never listened.
我說過我覺得PS4更好
I told you I thought the PS4 was better
但你從來不愿意聽我的  凱爾
but you never wanted to listen to me, Kyle.
你太過想當然了
You just had your head so set because...
因為Xbox玩家就是這樣的
because that's how Xbox people are.
那我們只有在黑色星期五見了
Then I guess I'll see you on Black Friday.
要是我在商場看到你了  凱爾
If I see you at the mall,Kyle,
我到時候不會手下留情的
I will have to try to beat you inside.
我知道
I know.
走吧  凱爾
Come on, kyle.
讓這些索尼玩家
Let these sony fuckers
沉迷于語音控制都很次的游戲機里吧
wallow in their limit voice control functionality.
圣誕節要來啦
Christmas is coming.
鵝都變肥啦
Goose is getting fat.
你在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
莎朗  你起來了
Hey, Sharon, you're up, huh?
我  好吧  聽著
I -- uh, all right, look.
我在商場找了份兼職
I took a temp job at the mall.
我只是想在節假日賺點外快
I just wanted to make extra holiday cash.
扯淡
Bubullshit.
莎朗  真的  我看到他們在招保安
I did, Sharon. I saw they were hiring extra security.
我就想這是個賺外快的好方法了
I thought it would be a good way to make money.
你這么做是為了在黑色星期五
You're doing this to try in getting in front of the line
能夠排在前面  是吧
on Black Friday, aren't you?
別人可沒這么認為  莎朗
Nobody else has thought of it, Sharon.
當大門打開時
I won't even be on the crowd,
我不會在人群中  我會在里面
I'll be on the inside when the doors open.
當大家把翔都快擠出來的時候
While everyone is trying to run over each other,
我會轉頭沖進商店里去
I'll turn around and run right into the stores.
我會是第一個進去買東西的人
I'll be the first to get whatever I want.
黑色星期五
Isn't Black Friday
不是意味著為別人買東西的嗎
supposed to be about buying things for other people?
凜冬將至  莎朗
Winter's coming, Sharon.
而我是一只卑鄙的小蜜蜂
And I'm a sneaky little bee.
艦長  推力是20%
The thrust are at 20%, Captain.
接近  發射戰爭一號
Engage and send War Factor One.
艦長  埃里克·卡特曼發來通訊請求
Captain, we have an incoming facetime request by Eric Cartman.
切換到大屏幕上
On screen.
伙計們  忙啥呢
Hey guys, what's up?
沒什么  我們正要檢查一顆M級行星
Nothing mate, we're just about to check out a class M planet
看看上面有沒有三鋰化物資源
that might have new source of trilithium.
天吶  這些家伙太呆了
God, these guys are such dorks.
問他們站在哪一邊
Find out who they're loyal to.
生生不息  繁榮昌盛
Yeah, live long and prosper.
伙計們  你們是Xbox玩家吧
Listen, guys, you're Xbox people, right?
盡管Xbox的幀率弱爆了
Even the Xbox sucks in framerate,
但我們還是只能說
we have no choice but to declare
它們從技術上講最適合我們的星際艦隊
they're most technologically fit for Star fleet.
天吶  他們太基佬了
Oh my god. They're so gay.
太棒了  那我告訴你們
Oh cool. What if I would tell you that
只要你們加入我們
we have a way for you to join us
就可以超低價買到Xbox One
and getting Xbox Ones super cheap?
便宜的Xbox One
Cheap Xbox Ones?
真的嗎
For real?
聯邦已經同意和我們并肩作戰
The Federation has agreed to fight with us.
有了他們和幼兒園的那幫人
With them and the kindergartners
我們的隊伍就有之前兩倍大了
our army has just doubled in size.
你還是覺得你可以說服斯坦加入我們
You still think you can convince Stan to come back to our side,
是嗎  凱爾爵士
don't you, Sir Kyle?
我不知道
I don't know.
你改變不了他的想法的  凱爾爵士
You can't change his mind, Sir Kyle.
索尼玩家是沒有理性的
Sony people don't think with logic.
他背叛了我們
He betrayed us,
而現在我們必須通過建立強大的聯盟
and now we must out Game of Thrones
來獲取這場權力的游戲的勝利
by making powerful alliances.
別逼我開口
Don't get me started.
我一直在追劇
I keep watching that show, and I'm still waiting
一直在等那些龍出來發威
for the damn dragons to show up and kick everyone's butt,
但我只等到了各種小雞雞
but all I get is wiener, wiener, wiener.
也不全是基友的小雞雞
It's not all gay wiener,
但只要出現了直男的小雞雞
but when they do show a straight guy's wiener,
就全是又軟又小的
it's all soft and floppy,
即使他媽的有個美女在面前
even when we just god damn have a pretty girl.
到底為啥
Why is that?
因為軟雞雞沒攻擊力啊
Because the soft weiner isn't threatening.
就跟基友的雞雞一樣
Just like a gay weiner.
巴特斯  你好像對雞雞有點癡狂
Butters, you seem to be somewhat obsessed with wieners?
我對雞雞癡狂嘛
I'm obsessed with weiners?
那對Xbox算啥
What about Xbo?
別搗亂  巴特斯
This isn't helping us, Butters.
索尼粉也許不是主要矛盾了
The Sony people might not be our biggest problem.
為啥
Why is that?
推特說圣誕將推出新的艾蒙玩偶
Twitter says they are introducing a new Elmo doll this Christmas.
什么新的艾蒙玩偶
What new Elmo doll?
節日里孩子們最想要什么禮物
佳節好禮品  隆重介紹別碰我艾蒙
Just in time for the holidays, it's "Stop touching me Elmo"
當你按壓他的背部
When you press his back,
艾蒙會把手放在你的膝蓋上說有趣的話
Elmo puts his hand on your knee, says fun things.
你大腿內側被撓過癢癢嘛
Have you ever been tickled on the inside?
寶貝  寶貝  你寂寞么
Honey, honey, are you lonely?
我能看你尿尿嘛
Can I watch you go potty?
你想親親給艾蒙配音的人嘛
Do you want to kiss the guy who does Elmo's voice?
別碰我  艾蒙
Stop touching me, Elmo.
艾蒙還能用牙膏擠擠樂陪孩子們刷牙
Elmo also helps kids brush their teeth with his toothpaste dispenser.
千萬別錯過這個節日最熱禮品哦
Don't miss out on this holiday season's biggest gift.
別碰我  艾蒙
Stop touching me, Elmo.
黑色星期五在南方公園商場首發
Available on Southpark mall starting Black Friday.
早啊  喬
Morning, Joe.
早  馬庫斯
Marcus.
早安  蘭迪
Morning, Randy.
這是什么鬼玩意
What madness is this?
怎么了
What is it, sir?
新品艾蒙玩偶
A new Elmo doll.
他們在黑色星期五發行新的艾蒙玩偶
They're releasing a new Elmo doll just in time for Black Friday.
天啊  不
Oh, Christ, no.
這是謀殺啊  冷血禽獸
You've murdered us, you soulless monsters.
簡直喪盡天良啊
You've killed us all.
上帝啊  他們已經開始排隊了
Oh, god, they're already lining up.
艾蒙
Elmo.
不是吧  這么早就開始排隊
No, they can't line up this soon.
簡直瘋了
This is crazy.
我來對付這幫禽獸
I'll deal with these demons.
如果你們是為黑色星期五折扣來的
If you're here for Black Friday,
隊伍在繩子那邊
the line starts on that side of the rope.
這根繩子嘛
This rope right here?
這是黑色星期五的專用隊伍
That's the line for Black Friday,
這樣其他人今天就能照常購物了
so that other people can do normal shopping today.
黑色星期五隊伍
好的  謝了
Okay, thanks.
艾蒙
Elmo.
給我艾蒙
Give me Elmo.
我們來尋求你們的幫助
We come seeking your help.
你跟Xbox粉是一國的
Do you side with those wanting Xboxes
還是想加入我們為PS4而戰
or will you join us on Black Friday and fight for PS4s?
你是認真的嗎
Are you for real?
你們心知肚明PS4是更好的選擇
You know that ther PS4s are the better choice.
這不明擺著嘛
I mean, come on.
我們當然選擇PS4
Of course we're going with the PS4.
他們更黑一點
They're blacker.
那就加入我們
Then join us.
我們需要人手幫我們在前20名內沖進商場
We need people to help us be the first 20 inside the mall.
我們要等PS4更便宜更多貨的時候
We are just gonna wait until the PS4s to be more cheaper and more available.
不  你們不能那樣
No. You can't do that.
你們不  不  不能那樣
You ca--ca--can't do that.
你們不明白這不僅關乎黑色星期五嗎
Don't you see that this is more than Black Friday?
戰線已被部署
Battle lines are being drawn.
等到最后別人都選擇了Xbox
If you wait it out but everyone else has already decided to go with Xbox, then
它就成了標準
that will become the standard.
那PS4就跟Betamax敗給VHS一樣輸了
The PS4 will be like Betamax was to VHS.
什么是Betamax
What's Betamax?
就像這樣
Exactly.
什么是VHS
What's VHS?
聽著  我們只是想讓玩PS4的人
Look, we are just asking people who want to play on
為他們的信仰而戰
PS4s to fight for what they believe in.
抱歉  我們就是漠不關心
Sorry, I guess we just don't care enough.
走吧  斯坦大人
Come on, Sir Stan.
一定有其他孩子會加入我們的
There must be kids somewhere who will join us.
麥考密克夫人  我想和你談談凱爾
Lady McKormick I was hoping I can talk to you about Kyle.
怎么了  公爵大人
Yeah. What is it, my Lord?
我不確定他心所向
I'm not sure if his heart is in the right place.
如果他叛變的話
If he were to ever switch sides,
斯坦軍就對我們造成了威脅
it could make Stan's army problematic for us.
但凱爾只是無名小卒
But Kyle isn't anything.
沒錯  但我們不能讓凱爾
True, but we can't let Kyle come
阻擋我們的正義之路
in the way of what's the right for the ours.
面對現實吧  麥考密克夫人
Let's face it, Lady McKormick.
這其實就只關于你和我得到Xbox One
This is really about you and me getting Xbox Ones.
其他人的存在只是為了
The others are simply there to
幫我們進入那幾扇門罷了
help us get inside those doors.
的確
Yeah. That's right.
你對其他男人
You have a strong influence over
影響甚大  麥考密克夫人
the rest of the men, Lady McKormick.
當時機成熟
All I'm saying is when the time comes,
我也許需要借用你的影響力
I might need you to use that influence
來搞定凱爾
to have Kyle taken care of.
我們達成共識了嗎
Do we understand each other?
很好  我想是的
Perfect. I think we do.
小屁孩  滾出我家后院
Hey, you damn kids, get the hell out of my yard.
草泥馬  這是安得拉特斯的花園
Fuck you, dude. This is the garden of Andrax.
這他媽是我家花園
No, it's my damn garden.
我受夠了你們這幫小屁孩在這
I'm sick of you kids dressing up and
過家家還探討背叛
having talks of betrayal in it.
嗡嗡  嗡嗡  嗡嗡
Buzz, buzz, buzz.
70英寸的電視
70-inch television.
真不錯  但是兩折的電腦
That would be good but 80% off a computer.
也許兩個都能到手
Maybe I will be able to snack both.
你還好嗎
Doing alright there?
很好  長官
Yes, sir.
抱歉  我沒想嚇你
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
沒有  我只是在看這些
No, I was just looking at
我買不起的東西
all These great things I can't afford.
我知道你為什么找這個兼職
Listen, I know why you took this part-time job.
是  是嗎
You--You do?
我能從你身上看到
I see it in you.
你關心他人
You care about people.
我也是  所以我每年都在這
Same reason I do it every year.
你讓我想起我兒子
You remind me of my son.
他死于89年的黑色星期五
He died on black Friday in '89.
大概我現在還想要救他
Guess I'm still trying to save him.
我只是想說  我...
Look, I just want to say I--
你這么做我非常感激
I really appreciate what you're doing.
我答應我老婆
I promised my wife
這會是我最后一次在黑色星期五工作
this would be the last black Friday I worked.
當我看到你這樣的人
When I see folks like you,
讓我對人類的未來充滿希望
it makes me hopeful that people will still be okay.
是  很好
Yeah, awesome.
媽的  不準在天鵝絨繩后面排隊
Aw, damn it, no lining up behind the velvet rope.
他們就是不聽
They just don't listen.
卡特曼的軍隊日漸強大
Cartman's army is getting bigger every day.
除了同盟孩子和幼兒園孩子
In addition to the federation and the kindergartners,
Xbox軍隊現在還擁有玩哈利·波特的孩子
the Xbox army now also has the kids who play Harry Potter,
運動員  游泳隊以及合唱團
the jocks, the swim team, and the glee club.
有消息稱六年級學生也都喜歡Xbox
Word is that the sixth graders all prefer Xbox too,
他們也會跟卡特曼組隊
and will team up with Cartman as well.
那我們這邊都有誰
And who do we have on our side?
除了我們  還有讀書會和賈妮思·平克頓
Besides us, it's the book club and Janice Pinkerton.
你有問過吸血鬼小子們嗎
Did you ask the vamp kids?
他們一直沒定
They're still undecided.
一定有辦法讓中立的人加入我們這邊
There has to be a way to get people on the fence to join our side.
PS
Playstation.
斯坦大人  或許該放棄了
Look, Sir Stan, it's probably time to give this up.
我們是將要滅亡的一代  斯坦
We're just a dying breed, Stan.
Xbox將會全盤通吃
Xbox is going to win this whole thing.
那我們就放任其他孩子決定
So we're just going to let other kids decide
我們用什么系統玩游戲嗎
which game system we all play on?
《權力的游戲》中會怎么做
What would they do on Game of Thrones?
事情到了最黑暗的境地  他們會怎么做
What would they do when things look their darkest?
[日語]
很抱歉打擾您  先生
Sorry, to disturb you, sir,
但我們覺得你該看看這個
but we thought you should see this.
"凜冬將至"
"Winter is coming.
"選好隊伍"
Choose side."
神馬玩意
只是美國中部的一個小鎮
Just a small town in middle America,
但很明顯一場戰爭在不斷升級
but apparently a war's escalating.
先生  如果這成為了新聞報道
Sir, if this were to become a news story,
而第一批進入商場的人都拿了Xbox
and if the first people inside that mall all got Xboxes,
會有損我們的企業形象
It clearly looks bad for our image.
這樣哦
這個黑色星期五
What's going to be the big item
人人勢在必得的大商品是什么
every one goes for this black Friday?
很可能是PS4
It just might be the Playstation 4.
索尼剛剛宣稱他們將提供
Sony has just announced they're offering
一個黑色星期五特別禮包
a special black Friday bundle
叫做"黑澀星期五俚包"
called the "brack Friday bunduru",
其中將包括四個控制柄
which will include four controllers,
一幅日本地圖  100美元回扣
a map of Japan, $100 rebate,
并且允許你自動提前預定《合金裝備5》
and allow you to automatically preorder for Metal Gear Solid V.
毫無疑問索尼已經提高了籌碼
No doubt Sony has just raised the stakes.
對  很好  同盟的孩子們
Yes. Good, federation kids.
你們在學習赤手搏斗
You're learning to fight with your hands.
繼續努力  幼兒園孩子們
Keep pushing, kindergartners.
凱爾爵士
Sir Kyle,
我知道索尼提供了黑色星期五俚包
I know that Sony's offering a special black Friday bunduru.
你清楚Xbox依然更好  對吧
You know the Xbox is still better, right?
對  但是Xbox為什么
Yeah, but why can't Xbox
不能讓你自動提前預定《合金裝備5》
automatically let you preorder Metal Gear Solid V?
凱爾爵士  提前預定毛都不能代表  好嗎
Sir kyle, preorder doesn't mean shit, okay?
你提前預定一個游戲
When you preorder a game,
就等于你提前付錢給
you're just committing to paying for something
那些加州的混蛋們
that some assholes in California
還沒有完工的項目
haven't even finished working on yet.
知道提前預定游戲得到的是什么嗎
You know what you get for preordering a game?
往嘴里塞個大雞巴
A big dick in your mouth.
黑色星期五  11月29日  南方公園商場
好了  聽著
All right, listen up.
商場不再允許人們
The mall's no longer allowing people
在感恩節之前為黑色星期五排隊
to line up for black Friday until Thanksgiving night.
沒有關系
It's okay.
為保持先后次序  我們會發放手環
To hold places in line, we're handing out wristbands.
天哪  天哪
Ahh! Oh, god! Oh, my god!
搶手環
Wristbands!
閃開  全都閃開
Back! Back all of you!
如果你們這幅德行  手環也不要發了
If that's how you are, there'll be no wristbands.
都走吧
Now go!
閃開
Back away.
我要給我兒子搶個埃爾莫娃娃  你這混蛋
I'm getting my son that Elmo doll, you fuck!
不
No.
你做的很好
You did good.
重任就交給你了
The watch is yours now.
不  你不能死
No. You can't die.
所有人都很喜歡你
Everybody really likes you.
這是我們的使命
This is what we signed up for.
是吧  我的朋友
Right, my friend?
不  我騙了你
No, I was lying to you.
我做這份工作是為了在黑色星期五搶占前排
I took this job to be at the front of the line on black Friday.
現在你知道事情的嚴重性了
Now you know how serious this is.
不管你最初的意圖是什么  保護這個小鎮
Whatever your intentions before, protect this town.
現在你是頭
You are in charge now.
拿著這個
Take this.
別讓黑色星期五成為末日
Don't let black Friday be the end.
都進去  我們有工作要做
Get back inside. We have work to do.
我們發起這場戰爭
When we started this fight,
是因為而我們受夠了
it was because we were tired of
玩Xbox的人跟我們說PS遜斃了
Xbox people telling us playstation sucked.
現在我們為自己戰斗
Now we're an army of our own.
我無法保證你們能活著回來
I can't guarantee you will live,
但我可以保證在一切結束之前
but I can guarantee that before this is over,
游戲機之戰的勝者將會見分曉
the winner of the console wars will be decided.
我們新任的領導者加入我們
Our new leader has joined us
以確保那個贏家是PS4
to help make sure that system is the PS4.
參見公主殿下
All hail the princess!
公主殿下
The princess.